Kingsley Solomon Ifijeh

Web Developer

Contact

Address

Lagos, Nigeria 100001

Phone

+2348100792853

E-mail

kinxly@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/kingsley-solomon-b9033

Skills

Code debugging

Responsive design

Website optimization

Technical Analysis

Requirements gathering

Project estimations

Agile Workflow

Tech Stack

 $\mathsf{HTML}\,,\mathsf{CSS}\,,\mathsf{Javascript}$

Java, Spring

React.js , Chakra , Next.js

Vue.js, Vuetify, Nuxt.js

Innovative Web Developer with 3 years of experience in website design and frontend development. Demonstrated talent for front and back-end web development to optimize online presence. A maestro in frameworks such as **React** and **Vue**, as well as scripting languages **Typescript** and **JavaScript**.

Work History

2021-09 -Current

Web Developer

Wewetube, Lagos, Nigeria

- Planned website development, converting mockups into usable web presence with HTML, JavaScript, AJAX and JSON coding.
- Engaged with clients to plan and optimize site issues and queries.
- Oversaw technical issues and troubleshooting requests to resolve user problems.
- Collaborated with stakeholders during development processes to confirm creative proposals and design best practices.
- Multi-tasked across multiple functions and roles to meet deadlines and organizational expectations.
- Collaborated with stakeholders during development processes to confirm creative proposals and design best practices.
- Contributed to projects within Scrum project management environments.
- Transformed native applications into mobile-friendly products.

2020-06 -2021-09

Front End Developer

Techstudio NG, Lagos, Nigeria

- Coded using HTML, CSS and JavaScript to develop features for both mobile and desktop platforms.
- Made recommendations for new technology integration based on suitability and alignment to business goals.
- Performed user experience quality assurance testing to identify and remedy shortcomings

2020-06 -

Code Instructor

2021-09 Techstudio NG, Lagos

- Teaching students basics of frontend development. i.e HTML, CSS
 Bootstrap and Javascript and React.
- Collaborated with students to complete homework assignments, identify lagging skills and correct weaknesses.
- Supported students with helpful study habits and exam strategies.
- · Worked on frontend of websites and Apps.

Education

2013-09 - 20170

Bachelor of Science: Industrial Chemistry

Bowen University - Osun, Nigeria

2006-09 -

High School Diploma

2009-10

Kith And Kin International College - Lagos, Nigeria